And then...
It's got five horns!
Hey, hey, Kaoru thinks orange would be good!
Nina likes orange too!
Orange it is~
Ah, how about we use it for the polka dots?
I like that!
That!
Ah! You copied me!
Hehehe...!
Ah! Waaait!
Jeez!
You're amazing, Koharu-chan...
You're like a designer!
Hm...
Do you want to color too, Chie-chan~?
N-no...
It's so cute, it'd be a waste...
Hm?
Wait, wait!
Woof woof!
B-be careful you two...
Are you okay?
Nina-chan!
Wahh~
Ehehe...
I'm okay!
Hm?
I'm sorry Nina-chan...
It's not your fault, Kaoru-chan!
Nina is okay!
Nina-chan...
I know~
Chie-chan, could you fix Nina-chan's clothes?
Eh?
Chie-chan is really good at sewing, after all~
That's... Someone like me...
Te to te o tsunaide
Hand in hand together
Kimi to issho ni niji no saki e
Together with you, beyond the rainbow
Takaramono o mitsuke ni
In order to find the treasure
Doa no mukou e dekakeyou
Let's go outside, past the door
Garasu no kutsu mo basha mo nai kedo
Though we don't have glass shoes or a carriage
Jitto shiterarenai
I just can't stay put
Tokimeki no oto takanaru
The beating sound of my heart
kodou no hari chikku takku
The pointer on my pulse goes tick-tock
Mahou no jumon wa kokoro ga shitteru
My heart knows the magic spell
Wakuwaku
So exciting
Hibiku merodii
The resounding melody
Kikoeru?
Can you hear it?
Mimi o sumashite
Listen carefully
Hajimaru!
It's starting!
Minna de "sutaato!"
Everyone's starting together
Hashiri dasou Let's go!!
Start running, let's go!!
Asa da yo ohayou! Asobou!
It's the morning, good morning! Let's play!
Sora ni egaku yume wa
The dream we'll draw in the sky
Taiyou yori mo mabushiku kagayaiteru
Shines brighter than the sun
Genki ni utaou! Odorou!
Cheerfully, let's sing! And dance!
Sekaijuu ni todoke
So that it reaches the whole world
Mirai o terasu hikari ni naru yo watashi-tachi
We'll be the lights that illuminate the future
Te to te o tsunaide
Hand in hand together
Kimi to issho ni niji no saki e
Together with you, beyond the rainbow
Kanaeru yo kiseki sae
As long as there are miracles that can come true
Kirakira ni Shine In The Sky☆
Twinkling Shine In The Sky☆
Episode 8 ~ What is it that you put on to become beautiful?
So, how are the kids?
You're getting more work than I thought you would.
Ahaha... Thanks to your help.
Ah, but...
Huh?
Ahaha!
Your way of thinking is so old school.
But of course I'm anxious!
Other groups that started around the same time
as us are already appearing on TV and stuff.
I was thinking we could
start off slow and steady, but...
Well, at any rate, we'll definitely want to do
a concert or something to raise awareness of them.
Do you think you can get
their parents' permission?
Well, I'm not sure if it's because they're busy
or what, but some of them are hard to reach...
Yeah, that'll happen.
But you know, parents nowadays will
complain about anything and everything,
so it's best to be cautious.
Good morning.
Ah, good morning.
So, anyway...
Ahhhh!
Section Chief!?
Ah...
About that project we discussed last week,
I've got a girl who seems like she's
gonna go viral that I want to assign to it.
Ah, um... Well...
Work!
Quickly!
Yes!
S-Section Chief...?
Here it is!
Wah!
So cool!
High Neck Sleeveless Dress
¥5200
(incl. tax)
356 people saved this as a favorite item
Black
S
In stock
Black
M
In stock
Black
L
In stock
Add to cart
She's sparkling like a princess~
Off-the-Shoulder Flare Long Dress
¥6800
(incl. tax)
242 people saved this as a favorite item
Pink
S
In stock
Pink
M
In stock
Pink
L
In stock
Add to cart
Wah, Chie-chan, this one's so cute!
Mmhmm!
A grown-up lady...
It turns out that Kiryu-san's brand
is doing a fashion show aimed at girls.
They're looking for models for it, apparently.
Kiryu-san's brand?
She's the president.
Eh!?
Huh?
She's a high schooler, isn't she?
She's our senpai as an idol, isn't she~?
But she's a company president?
They call her the charismatic high school
president idol, and she's really popular lately.
We hope that as many people as possible will learn about her passionate life.
In regards to her brand "Kasa Blanca"
"In order for me to further express myself,
to show who I am on the inside, I need to
start from the outside. That's how it all started –
At first it was hard, but even moreso fun,
I thought I'd open myself up to trying anything.
and it's my life, so I might as well, right?"
What's the secret behind the trifecta of being an idol, president, and high-schooler?
We hope that as many people as possible will learn about her passionate life.
In regards to her brand "Kasa Blanca"
"In order for me to further express myself,
to show who I am on the inside, I need to
start from the outside. That's how it all started –
At first it was hard, but even moreso fun,
I thought I'd open myself up to trying anything.
and it's my life, so I might as well, right?"
What's the secret behind the trifecta of being an idol, president, and high-schooler?
We hope that as many people as possible will learn about her passionate life.
In regards to her brand "Kasa Blanca"
"In order for me to further express myself,
to show who I am on the inside, I need to
start from the outside. That's how it all started –
At first it was hard, but even moreso fun,
I thought I'd open myself up to trying anything.
and it's my life, so I might as well, right?"
What's the secret behind the trifecta of being an idol, president, and high-schooler?
We hope that as many people as possible will learn about her passionate life.
In regards to her brand "Kasa Blanca"
"In order for me to further express myself,
to show who I am on the inside, I need to
start from the outside. That's how it all started –
At first it was hard, but even moreso fun,
I thought I'd open myself up to trying anything.
and it's my life, so I might as well, right?"
What's the secret behind the trifecta of being an idol, president, and high-schooler?
We hope that as many people as possible will learn about her passionate life.
In regards to her brand "Kasa Blanca"
"In order for me to further express myself,
to show who I am on the inside, I need to
start from the outside. That's how it all started –
At first it was hard, but even moreso fun,
I thought I'd open myself up to trying anything.
and it's my life, so I might as well, right?"
What's the secret behind the trifecta of being an idol, president, and high-schooler?
We hope that as many people as possible will learn about her passionate life.
In regards to her brand "Kasa Blanca"
"In order for me to further express myself,
to show who I am on the inside, I need to
start from the outside. That's how it all started –
At first it was hard, but even moreso fun,
I thought I'd open myself up to trying anything.
and it's my life, so I might as well, right?"
What's the secret behind the trifecta of being an idol, president, and high-schooler?
So, wanna try it?
I'll do it!
I will~
I-I got it!
When is it!?
Where is it gonna be!?
What about you, Sasaki-san?
Ah... Um...
Chie...
Let's do it, Chie-chan!
Okay... Chie will try her best too!
Alright, let's do our best together!
Yeah!
Ahaha!
Wahh~
It's so sparkly and clean~
Ah, Koharu-chan!
Ahh!
I'm sorry~
It's so easy to get distracted here, isn't it?
Be sure to introduce yourselves cheerfully, okay?
Okaaay!
This is so exciting!
So exciting~
Uhh, my shoes are...
Wahh!
Oh.
Hahh~
Ah...
Oh, you're here!
So pretty...
Ah...
Heh, thanks!
Good morning!
We're the Third Entertainment Division!
Thank you for having us today!
Thanks for having us!
Um, this girl here is...
Akagi Miria,
Koga Koharu,
and Sasaki Chie, right?
I'm Kiryu Tsukasa!
Let's put on a great show today, okay?
It's gonna be totally packed!
Wahh~
Hehe!
Is it just you here, Kiryu-san?
Yeah, I had everyone stay late
yesterday getting set up,
so I only have the bare
minimum number of staff today.
Isn't that rough on you?
Hm?
Isn't it my responsibility as their boss
to make sure my workers get adequate rest?
Producer-san?
I'll... help too!
Ah...
Ah, I mean...
Well, we came early, after all...
Or is that not okay?
Miria will too!
Wah~
What're we gonna do~?
C-Chie will help too.
Alright, now I'm feeling motivated!
Fine by me. I'll be sure to teach you the
Kiryu Tsukasa style of work!
Okay!
Tsukasa-san!
Hm?
The catering is here.
Ahh, it smells so good!
Wow~
Everyone, eat up!
Ahh!
Amazing...
It looks so good~
This is Heaven...
Wahhh!
So big...
This is where we're gonna be standing on stage...
It gets you fired up, doesn't it?
Hm?
It makes me shiver when I think about
how everyone's coming to watch!
Ah...
Miria will help you, miss!
Ah, so Miria's gonna help around the stage, then!
I'll leave it to you!
Okay, I got it!
Chie has to do her best too!
3rd Ent. Div. Makeup Room
They're so cute~
So frilly and sparkly~
Akagi Miria
Koga Koharu
Koharu
aki Chie
ki Chie
Tukasa
ukasa
Wahhh~
This dress is paired with
the white scrunchie and...
How's it coming?
Ah!
Is there anything you don't understand?
Ah...
Hey, Producer.
Y-yes!
Give me Chie.
Okay!
Eh!?
She does exactly what she's taught,
and most importantly...
She takes good care of the products.
Which means she's respecting the maker.
To Miria-chan
Please put on left hand.
Th-that's... I...
Sasaki-san!?
A four-day work week,
shortened hours to accommodate your studies,
and for payment, how does 160%
of what you're currently getting sound?
W-wait, no, no way!
Sasaki-san is an important member of our unit!
Ah...
Pft... Ahahaha! It was a joke!
Well, maybe in the future.
She was definitely serious...
Koharu, you'll come with me
to check the goodie bags, okay?
Hm?
Ahhh~
The fluffy pink...
You can wear it later!
Chie, I'm counting on you!
Yes!
Phew, this one's good too.
Man...
This sure is tiring, isn't it?
No...
Chie enjoys this kind of work.
Kiryu-san even complimented you for it!
Ah...
It's a cute dress, isn't it?
Yes.
It'd be a waste on Chie...
Were there any issues?
Phew...
Ah, no...
I see.
Anyhow, it's a bit late, but let's take a break.
Yes!
We can finally rest~
Hah~
Hahaha...
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Welcome back~
Miria-chan, here's some water.
Thanks!
Ah, where's Tsukasa-chan?
Ah, she's resting n–
Tsukasa-chan!?
A-ahhh...
I-if we take them to the cleaners right away...!
Then we won't make it in time...
Okay, let's do this!
Sorry for worrying you all!
I'll do something about this.
U-um... are you okay?
No, it's seriously so bad that I'm shaking.
Eh...?
But I'm a pro, after all.
A pro...
That's right.
She's shaking...
I have a duty to bring a smile to everyone's face.
No matter what kind of dumb mistake I make
backstage, I have to smile and get on stage!
In any case, I've gotta figure something out...
Ah, Chie-chan!
Could you fix it~?
Ah!
Chie-chan is super good at sewing!
N-no... I...
Is that right?
Eh...
U-um...
Ah...
Thanks, everyone.
But it was my mistake,
so I'll take care of it myself somehow!
Ahh...
Mm?
Sasaki-san!
Ah...
Producer-san...
Ahh, no, it's okay.
Okay...
Is there anything I can help you with?
B-but...
Producer is so busy, and rather than worry
about Chie, you should focus on everyone else...
I want to help you, Sasaki-san!
I'm your producer, after all!
Thanks for always thinking about everyone else.
But you don't have to
hold yourself back all the time.
Ah...
Chie was really happy when
everyone turned to her for help.
If somehow Chie could be of use to everyone,
then that would make me really happy.
Rooftop
parking is
closed today
Rooftop
parking is
closed today
keep everyone healthy
Everyone is so amazing...
If only Chie could be too...
But...
This is an important event for everyone, and I keep
thinking about what would happen if I screwed up...
And I get scared...
And it's all I can think about...
I...
Producer-san?
Pyon!
Don't cry, Chie-chan!
Or something...
Is this a bit too childish?
Hehe...
Yup!
Ahaha...
I get nervous easily too, so I'm sorry
that I can't give you any good advice...
You get nervous too, Producer-san?
Of course!
Even today, my heart's been pounding all day.
It's an important event for everyone, after all!
Sasaki-san...?
Ah...
Um...
I wanna do it!
I wanna make everyone smile too!
Yeah!
Hm?
Um...!
Please let me help too!
Wahh!
Ah...
Um, just a bit bigger...
Okay~
W-what do you think?
Kiryu-san!
If this fails, I'll wash dishes or do whatever
else I have to do to take responsibility.
Hey now, are you assuming it's going to fail?
I'll bring you what you need.
Please. Help me, Chie!
Fluffy hair
& flower corsage
Shorter
here!
Okay!
Kitto mainichi ga atarashii!
I'm sure every day will be new!
Donna ashita mo Brand New Page
For any type of tomorrow there's a Brand New Page
Suki na sutoorii mekutte hajimeyou
Let's start turning the page of a story I love
Minna ga motte iru yo jibun no sutoorii
Everyone has their own story to tell
Akogare no serifu o "
" (kakko) ni irete miyou
Let's try putting aspirational words in the "
"
Shippai wa seikou no fukusen ni naru kara
'Cause failure is a foreshadowing of success
Akutibu na ruuto ga dorama o tsukuru yo
Let's create a drama that takes an active route
W-we did it...
Junbi wa papatto ne furaingu ari janai?
Ready in a flash, aren't we off to a flying start?
Wahh~
So pretty!
Maenomeri no shisei saa ichi ni tsuite dondon yukou!
Let's lean forward, get into position, and go right way!
Look, Producer!
So sparkly~
It is!
Chie...
You're... the best...!
Ehehe...
Hajime no ippo de janpu shichae
Take the first step and jump
Yikes! We've got no time!
Tobidashita nara Brand New Stage
Once we leap out there's a Brand New Stage
Chie, come this way!
Swing shitara 1 · 2 · 3 de mune mo hazumu
When we swing in a 1-2-3, our hearts leap
Hm?
Kitto mainichi ga atarashii!
I'm sure every day will be new!
Donna ashita mo Brand New Page
For any type of tomorrow there's a Brand New Page
Noboru taiyou sutaato no aizu
The rising sun signals the start of the day
Sutaa dasshu☆彡 mae susume
Star dash ☆彡 let's move forward
Is Tsukasa-chan gonna come out soon?
Everyone, thanks for waiting!
Heheh!
Hm?
Mama, look, look!
So cute!
Hehe!
Wah~ Hehehe!
Hehehe... Wahh!
Ah...
U-um...
Hm?
Are you sure I don't look weird...?
Not at all! It looks great on you!
Um...
Hm?
Could you watch Chie?
Yeah, of course!
I'll be in the audience cheering for you!
Okay!
Sasaki-saaan!
Let's go together!
The sparkles are waiting for us~
Yeah!
Hehehe... Mwah!
One, two...
Unstoppable taikutsu o kanjisasenaide
Unstoppable, never letting me get bored
Memagurushii Days
Hectic Days
Sukejuuru tsumacchatte hai ni natteku yo
The more packed my schedule gets, the higher I feel
Kyuutenkai na kurai ga ii ne Every day
I enjoy the unexpected developments, everyday
Kanpeki o motome tsuzuketai no
I want to continue pursuing perfection
Itsudatte
Always
Fukakuteiyouso wa tanoshinda mon kachi nandesho
If you can have fun with the unexpected
3rd Ent. Div. Makeup Room
Thank you all so much!
Today's success is thanks to all of you!
Saikyou jan
you're unstoppable
It was super fun!
Ima wa mada manzoku nante dekinai ya
I still can't be satisfied yet
Ehehe... We got complimented...
It was so sparkly~!
That was so much fun!
Atashi ga ruuru
I am the rules
Hoshii nara kachitoru shika nai
If you want it, you have to take it for yourself
Chie.
Yes?
Misete ageru saikou no keshiki o
Let me show you the greatest scenery
Saisho kara zenryoku de oorai
Going all out from the start is alright
Won't you join me, after all?
I really want you!
Monokuro wa atashi iro ni
Turning monochrome into my own color
Mmhmm... Wai– again!?
Hibiku araamu kakugo wa dekiteru
The alarm rings, I'm already ready
Chansu wa hitsuzen
Chances are a necessity
I'm sorry.
Nogashitari wa shinai
I won't let them get away
Saigo ni warau unmei dakara
Cause it's my destiny to have the last laugh
Chie wants to be an idol with everyone.
I know zenbu ga hoshii no
I know I want it all
Wah...!
Dare ni mo agetakunai
I don't want to give this away
Ha... hahaha!
Wagamama de gomen
Sorry for being selfish
I see!
Atashi ga ruuru
I am the rules
Then, next time we meet, we'll be rivals, right?
I'll be waiting.
In the world of idols!
Ah...
Okay!
Dokidoki o hitohari zutsu
Stitching my nervousness thread by thread
Nuu you ni seichouchuu desu
I'm growing up as if I'm sewed together
Flower Corsage Dress
¥9800
(incl. tax)
242 people saved this as a favorite item
Modeled by Sasaki Chie
Blue
Fuan demo yuuki pachintte
Even if I'm anxious, I wear it with a clip of courage
Minitsuke kyou mo ganbaresou desu
so that I can work hard today
Hajimete no koto takusan atte
For the first time, we did lots of things together
Sukoshi kowai kara
I'm a bit scared, so
Chie-chan's
Sewing  Class
Issho ni... shite kuremasu ka?
can I... go with you?
Happi · happi · sooingu
Happy, happy sewing
Osoroi no kimochi sotto
These feelings gently come together
Chikuchiku suru no nandaka sugoku ureshii
They're prickly, but somehow I feel super happy
Ima wa asu no moyou tsukutteru tochuu
Now I'm in the process of making a pattern for the future
Otonappoi akogare no sutecchi
A mature, aspirational stitch
Chanto niau onnanoko ni jibun mo
I want to be like that kind of girl
Itsuka naritai na
myself someday